(Stone Coffin - 2)
Ching Sir, we got something.
What?
Just got word, a Hong Kong girl in her 20s
showed up at the Police station
and claimed she was Suet from
the stone coffin case.
Of her own free will?
Yes. She came to turn herself in
Don't move!
(Six months later)
Court!
Tai Yat-kin,
how did you meet the victim Lau Yue-bun?
Through a friend of a friend.
The banker wanted to make quick money.
I happened to know the owner of a casino
who wanted to launder money.
So I brought them together.
We started out OK.
After we split up the money a few times,
he got greedy.
We often got into arguments.
That loser made money all thanks to me.
He got so cocky, just knife him.
Don't do that. A waste of effort and energy.
Pour petrol on his hands.
Light him up and teach him a lesson.
Forget the lesson. Just kill him!
It was your suggestion to kill him?
No, I was just saying it.
When you're drunk, you're capable of
saying anything.
I was worried Dummy and Shek would
take me seriously,
so when I sobered up the next day,
I made sure I told them I was just kidding.
No, I didn't hear Brother Kin say
he was just kidding.
I didn't hear him say he was kidding.
I only heard him say "just kill him".
The next day, the dude came up on his own.
By "the next day",
you mean the day he was killed?
Yes, I went out with Dummy to get some food.
When we went back upstairs, we saw the dude.
Next time, remember to lock the door.
Right...
Hey! What are you looking for?
I came to get what is mine.
Your Brother Kin owes me $500K.
That's my money.
Who cares how much you're making,
as long as you're making money.
That's easy for you to say.
I'm the one living in fear.
If anyone found out, I'm going to jail.
Man the hell up!
What's a few years in the cell?
That's easy for you to say, you're not
going to jail.
I don't care. I want my money.
What are you doing?
Who made you the Boss? You have no say.
Dummy, get Brother Kin down here.
You, stay where you are!
Brother Kin...
The night before, Brother Kin got blasted.
Wake up, Brother Kin!
Ben is here...
I went upstairs to try to wake him...
He came for the money...
But I couldn't wake him...
There was nothing I could do,
so I went back downstairs.
Shek...
Let's figure out what to do.
I asked Shek if we were going to kill him.
But we didn't buy any tools.
Soon the dude found the safe.
Stop it! What do you want?
Stand back!
Stay back...open the safe!
I want my money!
I'll get the combination from Brother Kin.
Move...
Bloody hell!
Come out...
Dummy, get a rope and tie him up.
Tie him up!
We have rope?
Go find it!
Before we know it, something else happened.
Who is it?
(Unknown caller)
Are you the owner of LJ3314?
Your car is in my way.
Get over here and move it!
Or else I'm calling the Police!
Go move the car! Go...
OK, I'll go...
Hello?
I forgot the key!
What's wrong with you?
I'm taking it down now.
When is your friend coming?
Don't you know how to park a car?
He's coming...
What's going on?
Or else...
Look at the way he parked his car!
You wish to call the Police?
Officer!
I'm leaving...Sorry...
Coming...
Very sorry...
Move it...
Right...
We moved the car
and parked it as far away as possible.
When we got back to the industrial building,
Ben lost a lot a blood.
Is he dead?
People don't die so easily...
Why did you ram his head against the wall?
His head hit a nail!
It was Shek who grabbed Ben
and hit his head on the wall.
His head hit a nail.
Get Brother Kin...
The night before, I was up drinking
all night with friends.
I totally blacked out.
When I woke up, I saw Dummy and Shek...
They came upstairs and told me
they killed someone.
I went downstairs to take a look
and saw Ben lying by the wall.
There was massive bleeding behind his head
and he was dead.
They then decided to put the body
in a stone coffin
and throw it in the sea.
So I gave them a hand.
We didn't call for a ride.
What?
Wait downstairs.
A little bit off...
Come on...
Close the door...
Stop! Gotcha!
Your crate looks heavy.
It's huge. What's inside?
What's going on?
Nothing...just a misunderstanding.
You two...this is not the goods
for the client.
Go back in and get the right one.
Right...
Get out of the way...
You go ahead, sorry!
Sorry...excuse us...
Hurry up! Don't hold her up...
But we simply can't move the stone coffin.
We knew we can't keep it under wraps
for much longer.
So we planned to skip town.
If you were not involved in the killing,
why did you help them with hiding the body
and go on the run together?
That's brotherhood.
They're in trouble, I can't watch them fry.
Besides, a friend loaned me the unit,
if word go out about what happened,
I can't deny my involvement anyway.
You're not worried about getting arrested?
Yes, that's why we went into hiding.
We thought we could get away.
But the cops caught onto the
fake bank accounts,
and eventually found Ben's body.
Are you working for a criminal syndicate?
Who's the real boss?
I was a jailbird.
A petty thief like me won't know
any big shots.
I'm incapable of committing felonies.
I can't even kill a cockroach.
Your Honor, I wish to put Ho Pui-suet,
the immunized witness on the stand.
Ho Pui-suet, how did you meet
the victim Lau Yue-bun?
Strictly speaking, I don't know him.
I heard from Brother Kin, Dummy and Shek
they had an argument with the banker dude.
The banker dude should be Lau Yue-bun.
What were you doing at the time
of the incident?
I was sleeping upstairs.
Have you heard anything?
No.
The victim was downstairs arguing
and fighting
with Cheung Sai-chor and Hung Wai-shek.
You didn't hear the racket?
I always sleep with my headphone
and I turned it on full blast.
I really didn't hear anything.
Brother Kin...Stop sleeping...
Get up...we're all set!
We're done, Brother Kin...
Get up, Brother Kin...
What game is this?
It's not a game.
We killed Ben.
Seriously?
The body is downstairs. What now?
I don't know.
Suet, stay here. I'll go down
and check it out.
Hurry...
Hurry up, Brother Kin!
What now? When we went downstairs,
there wasn't so much blood...
You rammed his head.
I never actually saw Lau Yue-bun's body.
If you were not involved in the killing
and didn't know what happened,
why did you go on the run with them?
I didn't want to go.
But they said it'll be dangerous for me
if I stayed.
If the Police caught me,
I won't be able to clear my name.
We hid in a run-down guest house
and dared not go out
and we spent all our money.
We're going to get busted
and will be in jail for life.
I don't want to go to jail.
What now, Brother Kin?
Turning ourselves in is better than
getting busted.
We'll get a lighter sentence.
Man up and face the music.
They agreed to turn themselves in,
but were dragging their feet.
I couldn't take it any longer,
so I snuck out and went to the Police.
Witness, according to my client
Cheung Sai-chor,
two days before the killing,
did you and the three defendants
have a meeting to discuss
how to kill the victim
and how to get rid of the body?
Yes.
Forget the lesson, just kill him.
Killing him is the easy part.
What about the body?
Toss it into the Victoria Harbor.
The sharks will get him.
That's so boring.
Don't you have any new ideas?
I saw in a movie,
they put the body in a crate
and fill it up with cement.
You won't see the body again.
In the end, they used your idea
and put the victim in a stone coffin.
It wasn't my fault. I was just saying it.
I didn't expect them to kill anyone.
Why not?
Because they always brag
about murder and blackmail
but they never actually did anything.
How would I know they'd actually
kill the banker dude?
You said you took no part in
handling the body.
How come the Police found this
inside the stone coffin?
Is this your press-on nail?
No, I don't use press-on nails.
You're the only female in the unit.
Don't tell me this belongs to
the other defendants.
I don't remember. I stopped using
gel nails a long time ago.
Maybe Brother Kin brought other girls
to the unit and they dropped it.
I don't know. Don't ask me.
I'd like to ask the witness something about
the third defendant Tai Yat-kin.
You and my client Hung Wai-shek and
the second defendant Cheung Sai-chor
all admitted Tai Yat-kin said
"just kill him".
Does that mean killing Lau Yue-bun
was Tai Yat-kin's idea, right?
Yes, Brother Kin did say that.
But I'm sure he was just saying it.
When he sobered up the next day,
he made it clear to Dummy and Shek
he was just kidding.
Then why didn't you tell the Police
the first time you gave your statement?
They didn't ask me.
I'm telling you now because
you're asking me.
We found a bank transfer record of him
transferring money to you every month.
Can you explain that?
Brother Kin wanted me to be his secretary
to help them jot down the minutes
and he would pay me a monthly salary.
You never took part in any of
their criminal acts.
It was my client and the first defendant
Hung Wai-shek
who actually did the work.
How do you explain your pay
is several times more than what they get?
I don't know.
Let me ask you more directly,
what is your relationship with him?
Objection, Your Honor.
My client's relationship with the witness
is irrelevant to the case.
Of course it is relevant.
If the witness has an unusual relationship
with Tai Yat-kin,
her testimony is unfair to my client.
Overruled.
Witness, please answer the question.
What is your relationship with Tai Yat-kin?
Why are you protecting him?
We're sworn brother and sister, that's all.
And you sleep in the same bed?
Yes, we do. But he never touched me.
He never touched you.
Does that mean he wanted to have
sex with you,
but you turned him down?
No. We don't fancy each other.
So we didn't touch each other.
It's true. I'm not casual in that regard.
I don't even have a boyfriend.
If that's the case,
you should not sleep with a man
who's not your boyfriend, right?
I hereby pronounce,
the first defendant Hung Wai-shek,
is not guilty of murder.
but guilty of manslaughter.
He is sentenced to life imprisonment.
The second defendant Cheung Sai-chor,
is not guilty of murder
but guilty of manslaughter.
He is sentenced to life imprisonment
and remanded immediately.
The third defendant Tai Yat-kin,
is found not guilty of soliciting
to commit murder.
But he helped the other defendants
in disposing the body,
he's therefore guilty of preventing
the lawful burial of a body.
He is sentenced to ten months' imprisonment.
The immunized witness Ho Pui-suet,
the circumstances of her crime are
relatively minor,
considering her testimony against
the other defendants,
charges against her are dropped and
she is hereby released by the court.
I'm sorry, Shek.
You have been so sweet to me,
you think Brother Kin and I betrayed you?
Of course not!
Maybe I really didn't hear Brother Kin
telling us he was kidding when
he told us to kill Ben.
You know me, I only listen half the time.
Don't cry. It's not your fault.
I can only blame my own stupidity
for believing Brother Kin.
Don't blame yourself. It's not your fault.
Thanks for telling the court
I took no part in killing Ben.
That's why I was acquitted. Thanks.
Just tell me if you need help with anything.
Can you sell my phone and the game cards?
Then give the money to my mother.
I truly let her down.
(Several months later)
It's your favorite jasmine.
Can you smell that?
Cathy?
Ben?
Cathy, you're awake!
I'll get Dr. Chung!
Dr. Chung...
Cathy, you were in a coma for a few months.
You fell down the stairs.
You hit your head and had a concussion.
I checked, the fracture on your leg
hasn't completely recovered.
You'll need practice before
you can walk again.
But don't worry too much.
The key is to get enough rest.
If you need anything, just let us know, OK?
Get some rest.
Tracy!
I know what you're going to ask.
The baby is gone.
Thanks. You and the others
for taking care of me.
Don't be silly. You always took care of us.
You're alone and have no family.
It's sad to be in a hospital.
We'll all keep an eye on you.
By the way, who sent the flowers?
Mary did.
When you were in a coma,
she often asked me to take her in
a wheelchair to visit you.
When the flowers have wilted,
she'd urge me to buy fresh ones.
I want to see her.
You just woke up. You should stay in bed.
You know seeing me will make her better.
Come on, get me a wheelchair.
OK...I get it for you.
Mary has been in the rehab room
a lot lately.
She must really want to walk again.
She's been practicing hard.
Take it easy.
Slowly...small steps.
I quit. I'm a loser.
What's the point of practicing?
This is unnecessary. Why bother?
You only practiced for a minute last time...
Let me go in by myself...
Today, you've been up for five minutes...
I don't want to impose on you.
You should get back to work.
You can do it next time.
OK!
Have a nice chat.
I can't do this...
She is different when she's around you.
Let me go back to my room.
Thanks.
Let me go back to my room, OK?
OK...
Mary!
Cathy?! You woke up! You finally woke up!
Are you OK? You scared me to death!
I'm fine.
I've been asking Heaven the whole time
why am I being punished?
What have I done wrong?
Not only am I plagued with this rare disease
they also took from me
the two kindest people I know.
I kept praying to Heaven to let me
trade with you.
I'd rather die than watch you die.
Do you understand?
Your prayers have been answered.
Did you know
I woke up because I smelled
the jasmine you brought me.
You gave me strength. Thank you.
Ben was a fool.
He risked his life to make money
for a loser like me.
It was my fault. I'm so sorry...
No, I should be sorry.
Ben was anxious to make money
not just for you...
but also for our baby.
The nurse told me you had a miscarriage.
I thought I heard her wrong.
Trust me...I never intended
to use the baby to take Ben away.
I was selfish...
Don't...
I can't bear to have an abortion...
If you two decided to abandon me,
none of this would have happened.
Now that Ben is dead,
we are no longer connected.
You need not look after me anymore.
It's a nurse's duty to look after
her patients.
I chose this profession because I like it.
When we met, I didn't even know Ben.
I truly want what's best for you,
that's why I encouraged you
and took care of you.
I know you want to.
But I don't want to become a burden to you.
Ben liked jasmine because I like jasmine.
He gave you jasmine
and inadvertently gave away
our relationship.
When I was in a coma,
the smell of the jasmine you brought me
was the reason I woke up.
Don't you find it amazing?
Do you know why I like jasmine?
Its floriography is "you are my life".
You, me and Ben are destined to have
an important place in each other's lives.
That's why, with or without Ben,
you and I will move on with
our lives together.
The physiatrist said you're making
good progress.
See?
I'll soon join you in rehab.
You have no family, I'm all alone.
We'll support each other, OK?
Let's stop apologizing
and don't bring up the word "burden", OK?
Where are you? I need to talk to you.
I'll be home once I wrap things up.
Tai Yat-kin got ten months.
(Prettiest witness in stone coffin case)
Ho Pui-suet, the immunized witness
was acquitted?
Sorry about calling you so late.
I have something to ask you.
Gogo Sir, I read the certified copy
of the trial.
None of the defendants
said anything about Ben's phone.
That's because we couldn't find the phone
on Mr. Lau, in his car or at the
scene of the crime.
The two killers said
Ben's car was blocking another car.
The owner of the car called him
and the killers went downstairs to move it.
That means they should have kept the phone.
Maybe after they killed Mr. Lau,
they didn't want anyone to find him,
so they ripped apart the phone
and tossed it.
Normally, they admitted everything else,
they should admit this part as well.
Exactly! Don't you find that rather odd?
Also, Tai Yat-kin was only convicted of
"preventing the legal burial of a body".
I think there should be more to it.
Why?
Because I saw Ben got into
a fierce argument with him.
That was the last time I saw him.
We agreed on a 50/50 split.
The money is not enough.
Did you take my share?
$2M is not enough? You're too greedy.
What have you done?
You're just the go-between.
I did all the dirty work.
If things should go south, I'll go to jail.
I want $500K more.
The Boss trusts me.
If I didn't hook you up,
you won't see the money.
You should know who's calling the shots.
Fine! Get someone else to do it.
I won't take the next order.
Let's see how you explain to the Boss.
Listen, it's too late to back out now.
You want to quit? You won't get away.
I'll kill you if you quit.
He threatened to kill Ben.
I think he had a hand in it.
He might even be the mastermind.
Also, how could Ho Pui-suet be acquitted?
Because she was the immunized witness.
I know. But have you read her statement?
I think she was hiding something.
She said she has a platonic relationship
with Tai Yat-kin,
But I can tell you I have seen her before.
She told me she's on the pill.
Is it possible you're pregnant?
Of course not!
I'm on the pill. I don't have a baby.
There are so many questionable points.
You should re-start the investigation.
I'm not saying you're wrong.
But the Police work with evidence.
You can't possibly ignore
these questionable points.
No, but you must understand,
the case is a closed file.
Also, you should know no one
can be charged for the same offense twice,
unless there's new evidence.
But the things you said are not evidence.
They're merely your speculation.
Why take the pill if there's no guy...
Let's take a picture next to the nice logo.
Great!
Yeah...
Folks, I brought a friend.
Come...
New friend?
Sit down...
Nice...
Of course!
From the stone coffin case?
Sit...
You're so much prettier in person.
Stop teasing me.
The reporters won't care how I look.
They made my face as big as a pan!
They say you're working as a part-time
girlfriend right now.
Is that true?
No! I don't do that.
You have Instabook? I want to follow you.
Sure!
Me too.
Here...
Let's go...
Ten...Nothing...
Why are you phubbing over here?
Drink this.
I heard you're living with Bing, right?
I said...how do you like living with Bing?
Yes.
But sometimes when her boyfriend
sleeps over,
it's not too convenient.
Why don't you stay with me? I live alone.
I can't do that.
We're friends, right?
Don't argue. It's settled, OK?
Let me think about it. Thanks.
I want to buy your bag.
Where should we meet up?
Let's meet in Tsimshatsui East.
Nurse Tse, it's you!?
This is my first time on Comesaround.
But I spotted your bag right away.
I guess it's destiny.
Yes. Please check.
The bag is practically new.
I only used it a few times.
I'm only selling because I need the money.
This is nice. Let me try it.
How do I look?
It doesn't quite go with your style.
I want to try different styles.
Is this the girl band style?
Y2K.
You have Y2K clothes, skirts or shoes?
I'm OK with those.
You can sell them to me directly.
Save me the trouble of looking around.
When did they open the gel nail shop?
You want?
I always wanted to try.
What about you? You do nails?
I love it. But haven't done it in a while.
$400?! That's expensive.
Don't do it here. I can do it for you.
You know how?
Great!
This way is better for your nails.
I have done gel nails for too long,
that's why they break and chip easily.
What would you like?
Anything. I trust your taste.
There's something I want to say,
I hope you won't mind.
What?
When I bought your bag,
I recognized you from the stone coffin case.
I'm not sure if you want to bring it up,
so I didn't say anything.
My face was posted everywhere
and people criticized me.
It's impossible not to recognize me.
Don't worry! I don't believe those people.
I only believe in what I see.
The time we have spent together,
I found you quite simple-minded.
You're the first person who took my side.
Since the case came to light,
people didn't seem to mind,
but I know deep down they're afraid of me.
Brother Kin is not around,
I don't know who I can go to.
Brother Kin? The guy who's been nice to you?
Are you quite close?
You'll do anything he says?
Yes. I'll do anything for him.
One time, Dummy and Shek
bought chloroform,
I didn't know it stinks.
Brother Kin told me to smell it, so I did.
I felt so dizzy afterwards.
Tai Yat-kin tells you to say nothing,
you keep your mouth shut.
If he tells you to hide evidence,
you'll do it too.
Done!
It's nice!
Cathy, I need your opinion on something.
I met a guy at a bar...
He asked me to live with him.
You think I should?
It's not the first time you live with a guy.
Go ahead if you trust him.
OK!
Gogo Sir, Ho Pui-suet did
these nails for me.
Don't you think the pattern
is identical to the nail found inside
the stone coffin?
That means she took part in
handling the body.
Shouldn't you bring her in for questioning?
Unlike fingernails, press-on nails
have no DNA.
The pattern is similar, but you can't prove
the nail found inside the stone coffin
belonged to Ho Pui-suet.
At least you think they're similar.
The Chief is calling a meeting.
OK!
Hey, come here.
Look at Miss Tse's nails.
Are they similar to the one found
inside the stone coffin?
They're similar.
But that one had whiskers, this one doesn't.
They're not the same.
At least he thinks they're similar.
Unlike machines,
humans don't draw the exact same thing.
Anyone who walks in here
can refute your so-called evidence.
It comes off so easily,
even if the nail in the coffin
belonged to Ho Pui-suet,
it's also possible it fell out beforehand,
when those two were preparing the cement,
it got stuck somehow.
Are you sure you're not overthinking?
Sorry. Something came up. I need to go.
Suet...
What happened?
That guy I met earlier on...
I went to his place after happy hour.
He wanted to mess with me
and climbed on top...
I had to fight to get away...
You moved in with him?
I asked you last time,
you said if he's a nice guy,
I can move in with him.
I didn't know he was a creep.
Now I'm really scared.
I don't know who else to call.
Don't worry!
You came to the right person.
Come on...
Scumbag!
Let's go!
Don't be so gullible.
You must learn to protect yourself, OK?
I thought that creep would be like
Brother Kin
who felt sorry for me and took me in
and looked after me like a sister.
You're the only person I trust now.
You're so simple minded,
it's dangerous to be out there alone.
You should go home.
I don't have a home.
You don't?
When I was little,
Mom ran away with another man.
My old man was so pissed,
he used to hit me when he's upset.
Then he married another woman
who gave him a son.
The mother and son bullied me
and my old man never once defended me.
They're family, not me.
That's why I left.
I didn't even finish high school.
I know nothing.
Someone like me,
if I don't sponge off someone else,
how could I survive?
I can only blame myself for
being a bad judge of character.
Brother Kin was right about me, I'm stupid.
Hey! Don't say that.
Thanks for saving me just now.
If only you could have saved me last time.
Last time?
Yes! Remember I ran into you outside
the industrial building,
I stopped you on the street?
I didn't really want to pay you back.
Suet, it's time.
Go on ahead. I'll catch up.
Can you...
Suet, what's holding you up?
We have a plane to catch!
What?
Bye! Hurry...
You didn't want to go away with them.
When we first met, you took me to a doctor,
and loaned me money,
I knew you're a good person.
I was hoping you could help me ditch them.
It's over now. Let's forget it.
If you have nowhere to go,
would you like to stay?
You can sleep on the sofa.
Really? Thanks!
You're not feeling well?
No. I'm taking birth control pills.
But you said you're not with anyone.
Why do you need the pill?
The doctor prescribed them for my acne.
It can regulate my hormones.
That's right!
The pill has the effect.
Why didn't I think of that?
What did you say?
Nothing!
Here you go...
Wow?
What?
Your bracelet is really nice.
Let me help you...OK!
Thanks.
Good night.
You're up?
Sit down and have some breakfast.
Wow! What's with you today?
I didn't know you're a breakfast person.
I don't usually get up this early.
But I want to be with you.
I think eating breakfast with someone
is a very happy thing.
Really? I think so too.
Hurry up and try this.
OK, I'll try your cooking.
All set.
Not bad at all. You're really quite good.
Only because you have nice skin.
You're too busy to put on makeup.
Unlike me, this is the only thing I know.
If one can find something one is good at,
it's already something quite commendable.
You're the first person to
say that about me.
I think you can pursue a career
in makeup or styling.
Maybe this is your calling.
Suet?
I had a nightmare.
I need to sleep with someone.
Suet?
I always sleep with my headphone
and I turned it on full blast.
I really didn't hear anything.
Just like a kid.
Are you tired from work?
Everyone gets tired from work.
I may be tired,
but I haven't felt so good
in a long time.
Is it because of the sea?
Every time I'm at the seaside,
I felt really good
as if my troubles went away.
What are you doing?
Cathy, this is for you.
This?
Thanks for taking me in.
My boyfriend liked instant photography.
Why would someone young like you
like something so old fashioned?
Age has nothing to do with it.
You never know what you captured.
I like the surprise.
Hey...you'll make me look ugly.
You said you like the surprise.
My ex said the exact same thing.
Maybe you two think alike.
I should call you Auntie Suet.
That makes me sound so old.
Come on, let's take a picture of us.
OK!
Why did you make such a mess?
You're onto me?
I used your computer to search something
and I saw a file on the stone coffin case.
What do you want with me?
Yes, I want to know exactly how Ben died.
Was it simply manslaughter?
Or there was more to it?
Why do you want to know?
Who is he to you?
No wonder I found these...
You were having an affair.
Yes!
He was married.
You seem honest, why do you want
to be the other woman?
Why Ben and I were together
is something you'll never understand.
I was wrong. I failed his wife.
But I'm trying my best to look after her.
I want to know the truth
not just for myself.
I'm also doing this for Mary.
I thought I met a big sister
who genuinely cares about me.
But you were using me the whole time.
You're worse than the rest of them.
I suspected you at first,
but I eventually found out
your world is very simple.
People were using you. You were innocent.
I guess the time we spent with each other,
you should be able to sense
everything I told you was the truth.
I truly considered you as a friend.
I'm telling you for the last time.
I told the court everything I knew.
Whatever you want to know, just ask me.
Don't sound me out.
Don't worry, I won't.
Don't lie to me anymore.
I trust you are a good person.
I don't want to lose faith in you.
I have nothing to hide from you.
(The next day)
Everyone wants to make quick money.
Phone scams have high return and low risks.
Brother Kin, I brought your
favorite egg tarts.
Go get me a pack of smokes.
OK.
Don't eat them all. They're too sweet.
You have diabetes.
So? I have medication.
How's the girl?
I had her wrapped around my fingers.
Luckily, you taught me what to do.
Luckily I didn't let those two clowns
toss Ben's phone
and sent you to get it unlocked.
What about his phone?
I'll take it outside and ditch it.
No. Don't let anyone find it.
I'll take care of it.
Can you unlock this?
Did you unlock the phone I brought in?
All set.
Thanks.
What is it?
Brother Kin, Ben's chick approached me.
She's always sounding me out.
I kept shooting off my mouth.
I can't remember if I said the wrong thing.
So? We know more about her.
She should be worried.
What about the thing I asked you to do?
I followed your instructions
and tried to find out where the money was.
Did you leave me the keycard?
Yes, it's for you.
Is this about the legal loopholes?
Don't ask. Just keep it for me.
I read all the messages.
I only know he gave the money
to his girlfriend.
I didn't know it was Cathy.
Ben was quite smart.
No wonder the cops couldn't trace the money.
Since he's dead, we should split the money.
How?
Pretend you didn't know who she was.
Stick with her
and try to find out
where she kept the money.
But to tell a lie like that,
what if she saw through me?
You're so adorable and good at
sweet talking people.
No one would suspect you of
harboring any ulterior motives.
But what's taking so long?
You've been looking since I was in jail.
Now I'm out and you still haven't found it.
I searched through the whole flat.
No money, no keycard.
She almost caught me.
Luckily, I made up a story.
Then it's safe to keep looking.
I'm afraid if I keep it up,
Cathy will ignore me.
Not if you found the money.
I'll take care of you if she won't.
I'll look after you, silly.
Don't tell me you're taking this seriously.
You think she's your friend?
Don't forgot how Ben died.
Don't you feel guilty when you see her?